Who says you can't
go home again?
Oh!
Yeah!
Say it.
Say what you said every
time you tortured me!
Say it!
Blessed are the wicked who
are healed by my hand!
Blessed are the wicked...
who are healed...
by my hand.
You commie motherfucker!
Oh, my God. Did you
feel that, too?
Only best buddies execute
pedophiles together.
You got 30 seconds, you
jabbering butt plug!
Now we're getting it.
I need a bus to get
you all out of here.
Orphans.
Oh, geez.
It's time to burn for
what you've done!
A child should not be
burdened with such power!
Russell! Wait!
Oh!
Wait! He hasn't
killed anyone yet!
What more do you need to see?
Don't you fucking dare!
He's just a kid!
Tick, tock. Meter's running!
I'm gonna melt you down
and make a cock ring.
I told you! Leave me alone!
Come on!
Listen to me!
That's how we do it
in Mother Russia.
They say millennials are
the hardest to reach.
Oh, no. You're doing amazing.
Damn, it feels good
to be a gangsta!
Go home, Wade!
You're ruining everything!
I'm getting good at this shit.
Go, go, go!
He dies tonight, Wade.
You can't stop me!
He even runs like a
fucking pervert.
Like an online predator
who lost his laptop.
There's one bullet
left in that gun.
Wait, wait, wait! Please,
just give me a second!
I got this.
Russell! Stay back!
Go home, Wade!
Let's talk. It doesn't
have to go this way!
That piece of shit...
he deserves to die for
what he did to you.
He hurt you badly. Makes
you wanna hurt others.
But if you kill him, he wins.
You become everything he
says you are, but worse.
You're just a kid.
You don't wanna hurt anyone.
How do you know what I want?
Because I've been inside you.
That came out wrong.
I've been inside your shoes.
Which is also off-putting.
It's not a great analogy.
The point is...
there are people...
There are people in
this fucking world...
besides him, who will
treat you right.
It isn't too late. Don't do it.
I never should've
left you there.
I never should've left
you in that prison.
I can't trust you.
I can't trust anybody!
Wonderful kid.
You can't stop me, Wade!
I got one more idea.
It's just a really bad
one, even for me.
Wade, what are you doing?
All right. This is for
all the marbles, kid!
You're gonna kill
someone today...
Blessed are the wicked...
then it's gotta be me.
Who are healed by my hand!
Fuck this!
Tell me they got
that in slow motion.
Oh, that's not good.
No, sir.
You sacrificed yourself for me.
Yeah.
And it was the best
thing I ever did.
I told you I care about you.
You're a good kid, Russell.
Hey.
The bear.
It worked.
Because of you.
No, Wade, because of you.
Stop, stop, stop!
Stop!
Just let it happen, okay?
I guess my heart was finally
in the right place.
That riddle is so fucked up.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Don't be. Don't be.
I've been trying to make
this happen for a while.
Please, just don't leave me.
I don't wanna die
without an audience.
We are not going anywhere.
Oh, God, I hope the
Academy is watching.
Just rest, okay?
Papa.
♪ Papa, can you hear me? ♪
♪ Papa, can you find
me in the night? ♪
Before I go...
Sorry, I got a bit more in me.
Domino.
I want you to have my
Adventure Timewatch.
Turns out that I'm
the lucky one.
Thank you.
Hey, Sabrina, the Teenage Witch.
I liked you better
with your hair short.
Think everyone did.
Hi, Yukio. Hi, Wade!
And you...
Chrome Bone.
I haven't always been
the best friend to you.
But you've always
been that to me.
So thank you.
Say "fuck" for me.
Just once. Come on,
we'll do it together.
It's no big deal.
Here we go. One, two, three.
F... F... F...
Fuck.
Wow! Enjoy hell, swamp mouth.
And you, Cable.
You get back to your family.
You tell 'em Wade says hi.
And promise me.
Promise me one thing.
That you'll start
judging people...
not by the color of their skin,
but by the content
of their character.
Jesus. WADE: R-Dog?
There you are. Hey!
You're a superhero now, bubba.
That's why it's high time
that you had a super suit.
This one is yours.
You might wanna get
it steam cleaned.
Especially around the pants.
And let it out a
little in the waist.
But, hey.
Look.
Family is not an F-word.
All right?
There's one out there for you.
Just keep looking, okay?
Guys, for a second there...
we made a pretty good team.
Oh, it's so hard to go.
I just love being around
you guys so much.
So, so much.
Mmm.
No, I can feel it now.
Here it comes, yeah.
I feel the soul
exiting the husk.
Yeah.
Can you see it?
Do you see that
beautiful bright light?
There it is.
Oh, that's the sun.
Don't stare directly into that.
I just have a few final words.
Woodpecker.
Gingivitis.
Codswallop.
Do You Want to Build a Snowman?
Sorry I'm late.
There was a bunch
of handicapable children
who were stuck in a tree.
No.No.
But I did have to
help a kid.Yeah.
He's got a terrible name.
It's just awful.
Ugh. I tried to tell him.
Is this heaven?
It is now.
I am so sorry.
It's okay.
I missed you so much.
What is it? What's wrong?
It's not time.
What do you mean it's not time?
I'm here, I made it.
You can't stay. No, no, no.
I'm staying. I'm not going
anywhere without you.
It's okay.
There's a time for us.
It's just not now.
They need you. Who?
Your F-word.
Why?
You'll find out.
It's all right. I'll be here.
It's pretty fucking
awesome over here.
I can have anything I want.
Can every day be
International Women's Day?
It is heaven.
I love you.
I know. I love you, too.
Now, go.
Go on. Go, get out of here.
Go.
Hey!
Kiss me like you miss me, Red.
Well, come here.
Don't fuck Elvis.
Ooh, too late. I'm sorry?
Time to make the chimichangas.
30 seconds.
Hey. Been meaning to ask you...
what's with the creepy,
dirty hobo bear?
It's my daughter's teddy bear.
Her name's Hope.
Well...
What are you doing?
Somebody swiped right.
Tell me they got
that in slow motion.
You sacrificed yourself for me.
It would seem I...
Huh?
Genuine, high-grade lead.
You time-sliding son of a bitch!
You did this for me?
Wait. You can't go back.
You used the last of your fuel.
What about your girl, your wife?
Now, my family's safe. And
I didn't do it for you.
No, I'm gonna stick
around for a while...
and make sure the world
doesn't shit itself
into oblivion.
No. You did it for me.
No, I didn't.
You did. I really didn't.
Pretty sure you did. No,
I'm positive I didn't.
Fine. All right, let's flip a coin.
Okay?
Heads, you did it for me.
Tails, you did it for me.
I'm not even gonna look,
because you did it for me.
Say it again.
He did it for me. CABLE: Jesus.
We must get the collar off.
Forget it. It's no use.
These collars don't
just come off.
Wade.
I have an idea.
No, no, no! Let's not do that.
Please!
I'd rather die of cancer.
Let's just...
Oh, God! They do say the pen
is grosser than the sword.
We need the code.
Try, uh, seven?
Settle down, Captain Lucky.